1. Statement - productName = SCHEDULE_SIMPLE_PRODUCT
5. Statement - regularPrice = SCHEDULE_REGULAR_PRICE
9. Statement - salePrice = SCHEDULE_SALE_PRICE
13. Statement - quantity = 6
17. Statement - subtotalRegular = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, regularPrice)
21. Statement - subtotalSale = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(1, salePrice)
25. Statement - shippingType = "free"
29. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
33. Statement - shippingTypeSale = "normal"
37. Statement - shippingLabelSale = SHIPPING_LABEL
41. Statement - shippingPriceSale = SHIPPING_PRICE
45. Statement - totalSale = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", subtotalSale + shippingPriceSale))
49. Statement - schedulTimeout = 300
53. Statement - limitStockSchedule = "yes"
57. Statement - variation = new org.json.JSONArray()
61. Statement - scheduleDelay = 4
65. Statement - scheduleDuration = 4
69. Statement - paymentMethod = "Amazon Pay"
75. Login as Admin
79. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
83. beautytap.AdminAction.selectAdminMenu
87. Statement - datetime = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.generateScheduleDateTime(TIMEZONE, scheduleDelay, scheduleDuration)
91. Statement - startDate = datetime.get("startdate")
95. Statement - endDate = datetime.get("enddate")
99. beautytap.AdminAction.scheduleSaleProduct
103. closeBrowser
109. VP1: Verify before schedule, regular price display on Search result
113. beautytap.ShopAction.globalSearch
117. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnSearchResult
123. VP2: Verify before schedule, regular price display on Product Detail
127. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductDetails
133. VP3: Verify before schedule, regular price display on Product List
137. beautytap.ShopAction.findProductOnProductList
141. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnProductList
147. Add product to cart
151. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
157. Go to cart
163. VP4: Verify before schedule, regular price display in cart
169. Checkout via amazon pay
175. VP5: Verify before schedule, regular price display in Checkout
179. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray(productArray)
183. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyOrderDetailsOnCheckout
187. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaAmazonPay
193. VP6: Verify before schedule, regular price display in Order Received
199. Wait for schedule
205. VP7: Verify during schedule, SALE price display on Search result
209. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnSearchResult
215. VP8: Verify during schedule, SALE price display on Product Detail
219. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductDetails
225. VP9: Verify during schedule, SALE price display on Product List
229. beautytap.ShopAction.findProductOnProductList
233. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnProductList
239. VP10: Verify during schedule,Quantity textbox is not displayed due to limit stock affect
245. Add product to cart
249. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
255. Go to cart
261. VP11: Verify during schedule, SALE price display in cart
267. Checkout via amazon pay
271. beautytap.ShopAction.loginAmazonPay
277. VP12: Verify during schedule, SALE price display in Checkout
281. Statement - productSale = new org.json.JSONArray(productArraySale)
285. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyOrderDetailsOnCheckout
289. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaAmazonPay
295. VP13: Verify during schedule, SALE price display in Order Received
301. Wait for schedule
307. VP14: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display on Search result
311. beautytap.ShopAction.globalSearch
315. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnSearchResult
321. VP15: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display on Product Detail
325. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductDetails
331. VP16: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display on Product List
335. beautytap.ShopAction.findProductOnProductList
339. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnProductList
345. Add product to cart
349. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
355. Go to cart
361. VP17: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display in cart
367. Checkout via amazon pay
373. VP18: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display in Checkout
377. Statement - productsAfter = new org.json.JSONArray(productArrayAfter)
381. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyOrderDetailsOnCheckout
385. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaAmazonPay
391. VP19: Verify AFTER schedule, regular price display in Order Received
395. closeBrowser