1. Statement - username = USER_EMAIL
5. Statement - password = USER_PASSWORD
9. Statement - productName = SIMPLE_PRODUCT
13. Statement - price = SIMPLE_PRODUCT_PRICE
17. Statement - quantity = 3
21. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
25. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
29. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
33. Statement - total = subtotal + shippingPrice
37. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":"","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
41. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + username) + "}))
45. Statement - paymentMethod = "PayPal"
49. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
53. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
57. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
61. beautytap.GeneralAction.selectProfileMenu
67. Get current multiplier, lifetime, pending, redeemable points, point value
71. Statement - multiplier = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("multiplier"))
75. Statement - currentlevel = objReward.get("currentlevel")
79. Statement - lifetime = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("lifetime"))
83. Statement - pending = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pending"))
87. Statement - redeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("redeemable"))
91. Statement - pointvalue = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pointvalue"))
95. Statement - format = new java.text.DecimalFormat(0.##)
99. Statement - rewardEarned = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(format.format(multiplier * subtotal))
103. Statement - notificationMessage = "You received " + rewardEarned + " redeemable points"
109. Buy a product
113. beautytap.ShopAction.selectSearchResult
117. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
121. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
127. Process to checkout
131. beautytap.ShopAction.fillCustomerInformation
137. VP1: Verify order details on checkout
143. VP2: Verify reward on checkout page: Rewards earned = (subtotal-discount)*multiplier
147. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaPaypal
153. VP3: Verify order details on Order Recieved
159. VP4: Verify reward on Order received page: Rewards earned = (subtotal-discount)*multiplier
163. Statement - orderInfo = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.getOrderInfoOnOrderReceived()
167. Statement - orderNumber = orderInfo.get("ordernumber")
171. Statement - orderDate = orderInfo.get("date")
175. Statement - completeOrderSubject = "Your " + SITE_TITLE + " order from " + orderDate + " is complete"
179. Statement - completeOrderSubject = completeOrderSubject.replace("[", "").replace("]", "")
185. Go to My Rewards page
191. VP5: Verify reward detail: lifetime=no change,pending=current pending+reward, redeemable=no change,point value: no change
195. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardPointsDetails
201. VP6: Verify reward history: 1 row with sataut pending,1 row with status processing
205. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardHistory
211. Logout
217. Login As Admin
221. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
227. Go to Woocommerce > Orders > Change order status to Completed
231. beautytap.AdminAction.changeOrderStatus
237. VP7: Verify user recieve notification email with redeemable point
241. beautytap.GeneralAction.verifyEmailExist
245. beautytap.GeneralAction.openEmail
249. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyOrderCompleteEmail
255. Logout
261. Login again
265. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
269. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
275. VP8: Verify notification: You received [#] redeemable points
281. Go to My Rewards page
287. VP9: Verify reward detail: lifetime=lifetime+reward,pending=pending-reward, redeemable=redeemable+reward,point value: associate with reward
291. Statement - newRedeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", redeemable + rewardEarned))
295. Statement - newPointValue = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateLoyaltyPointValue(newRedeemable)
299. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardPointsDetails
305. VP10: Verify reward history: 1 row with sataut complete
309. beautytap.GeneralAction.logout