1. Statement - productName = SCHEDULE_SIMPLE_PRODUCT
5. Statement - regularPrice = SCHEDULE_REGULAR_PRICE
9. Statement - salePrice = SCHEDULE_SALE_PRICE
13. Statement - quantity = 6
17. Statement - subtotalRegular = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, regularPrice)
21. Statement - subtotalSale = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(1, salePrice)
25. Statement - shippingType = "free"
29. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
33. Statement - shippingTypeSale = "normal"
37. Statement - shippingLabelSale = SHIPPING_LABEL
41. Statement - shippingPriceSale = SHIPPING_PRICE
45. Statement - totalSale = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", subtotalSale + shippingPriceSale))
49. Statement - schedulTimeout = 300
53. Statement - limitStockSchedule = "yes"
57. Statement - variation = new org.json.JSONArray()
61. Statement - scheduleDelay = 4
65. Statement - scheduleDuration = 4
69. Statement - paymentMethod = "Amazon Pay"
75. Login as Admin
79. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
83. beautytap.AdminAction.selectAdminMenu
87. Statement - datetime = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.generateScheduleDateTime(TIMEZONE, scheduleDelay, scheduleDuration)
91. Statement - startDate = datetime.get("startdate")
95. Statement - endDate = datetime.get("enddate")
99. beautytap.AdminAction.scheduleSaleProduct
103. closeBrowser
109. VP1: Verify before schedule, regular price display on Search result
113. beautytap.ShopAction.globalSearch
117. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductOnSearchResult
123. VP2: Verify before schedule, regular price display on Product Detail
127. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductDetails