1. Statement - productName = VARIATION_PRODUCT
5. Statement - price = VARIATION_PRICE1
9. Statement - variation = VARIATION_NAME1
13. Statement - r_string = new java.lang.Math().random().toString().substring(2, 8)
17. Statement - email = "auto" + r_string + "@mailinator.com"
21. Statement - orderNote = "auto" + r_string + "Order"
25. Statement - currentNumberItemInCart =
29. Statement - quantity = 8
33. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
37. Statement - total = subtotal
41. Statement - total = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(1, total)
45. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":") + variation) + ","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
49. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + email) + "}))
53. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_EMS_SHIPPING_LABEL
57. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
61. Statement - shippingType = "freeEMS"
65. Statement - paymentMethod = "Amazon Pay"
69. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
73. beautytap.ShopAction.globalSearch
79. VP1: Verify product display in search result panel with regular price
83. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductOnSearchResult
87. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductVariation
93. VP2: Verify product detail page display with regular price
97. Statement - currentNumberItemInCart = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.getNumberItemInCart()
101. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
107. VP3:Verify product is added to card: cart number increase and message display “PRODUCT_NAME” has been added to your cart.
111. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductIsAddedToCart
115. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
121. VP4:Verify product is added to cart with correct price and quantity
125. beautytap.ShopAction.processToCheckout
131. Login amazonPay
137. VP5: Verify order details on checkout page
143. Checkout via amazonPay
149. VP6: Verify order details on order received Page
153. closeBrowser