1. beautytap.AdminAction.deleteUser
5. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
11. SIGNUP VIA FACEBOOK NOT EXIST IN SYSTEM
15. beautytap.GeneralAction.signupViaFacebook
21. VP1: Verify user is logged in after Signup via Facebook
25. beautytap.GeneralAction.logout
31. LOGIN VIA FACEBOOK NOT EXIST IN SYSTEM
35. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
39. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
43. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
49. VP2: Verify user is logged in via Facebook
53. beautytap.GeneralAction.logout
59. SIGNUP VIA FACEBOOK ALREADY EXIST IN SYSTEM
63. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
67. beautytap.GeneralAction.signupViaFacebook
73. VP3: Verify user is logged in after Signup via Facebook