1. Statement - productName = SIMPLE_PRODUCT
5. Statement - price = SIMPLE_PRODUCT_PRICE
9. Statement - r_string = new java.lang.Math().random().toString().substring(2, 8)
13. Statement - email = "auto" + r_string + "@mailinator.com"
17. Statement - orderNote = "auto" + r_string + "Order"
21. Statement - currentNumberItemInCart =
25. Statement - quantity = 3
29. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
33. Statement - total = subtotal
37. Statement - total = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(1, total)
41. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":"","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
45. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + email) + "}))
49. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
53. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
57. Statement - shippingType = "free"
61. Statement - paymentMethod = "PayPal"
65. Statement - category = "What's New"
69. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
73. beautytap.ShopAction.selectCategory
77. beautytap.ShopAction.findProductOnProductList
83. VP1: Verify product display on product list
87. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductOnProductList
93. VP2: Verify product detail page display with regular price
97. Statement - currentNumberItemInCart = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.getNumberItemInCart()
101. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
107. VP3:Verify product is added to card: cart number increase and message display “PRODUCT_NAME” has been added to your cart.
111. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyProductIsAddedToCart
115. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
121. VP4:Verify product is added to cart with correct price and quantity