1. Statement - username = USER_EMAIL
5. Statement - password = USER_PASSWORD
9. Statement - productName = SIMPLE_PRODUCT
13. Statement - price = SIMPLE_PRODUCT_PRICE
17. Statement - quantity = 3
21. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
25. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
29. Statement - pointUsed = 60
33. Statement - pointValueUsed = 2
37. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
41. Statement - subtotalApplyReward = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", subtotal - pointValueUsed))
45. Statement - total = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", subtotal - pointValueUsed + shippingPrice))
49. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":"","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
53. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + username) + "}))
57. Statement - paymentMethod = "PayPal"
61. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
65. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
69. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
73. beautytap.GeneralAction.selectProfileMenu
79. Get current multiplier, lifetime, pending, redeemable points, point value
83. Statement - multiplier = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("multiplier"))
87. Statement - currentlevel = objReward.get("currentlevel")
91. Statement - lifetime = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("lifetime"))
95. Statement - pending = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pending"))
99. Statement - redeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("redeemable"))
103. Statement - pointvalue = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pointvalue"))
107. Statement - rewardEarned = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", multiplier * subtotal - pointValueUsed))
113. Buy a nother product and use reward point
117. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductOnSearchResult
121. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
125. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
131. Process to checkout
137. Apply Reward point
143. Fill customer information
149. VP1: Verify Order details on checkout page with reward discount