1. Statement - username = USER_EMAIL
5. Statement - password = USER_PASSWORD
9. Statement - productName = SIMPLE_PRODUCT
13. Statement - price = SIMPLE_PRODUCT_PRICE
17. Statement - quantity = 3
21. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
25. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
29. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
33. Statement - total = subtotal + shippingPrice
37. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":"","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
41. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + username) + "}))
45. Statement - paymentMethod = "PayPal"
49. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
53. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
57. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
61. beautytap.GeneralAction.selectProfileMenu
67. Get current multiplier, lifetime, pending, redeemable points, point value
71. Statement - multiplier = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("multiplier"))
75. Statement - currentlevel = objReward.get("currentlevel")
79. Statement - lifetime = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("lifetime"))
83. Statement - pending = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pending"))
87. Statement - redeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("redeemable"))
91. Statement - pointvalue = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objReward.get("pointvalue"))
95. Statement - rewardEarned = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", multiplier * subtotal))
99. Statement - notificationMessage = "You received " + rewardEarned + " redeemable points"
105. Buy a product
109. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductOnSearchResult
113. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
117. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
123. Process to checkout
127. beautytap.ShopAction.fillCustomerInformation
133. VP1: Verify order details on checkout
139. VP2: Verify reward on checkout page: Rewards earned = (subtotal-discount)*multiplier
143. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaPaypal
149. VP3: Verify order details on Order Recieved
155. VP4: Verify reward on Order received page: Rewards earned = (subtotal-discount)*multiplier
159. Statement - orderInfo = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.getOrderInfoOnOrderReceived()
163. Statement - orderNumber = orderInfo.get("ordernumber")
167. Statement - orderDate = orderInfo.get("date")
171. Statement - completeOrderSubject = "Your " + SITE_TITLE + " order from " + orderDate + " is complete"
175. Statement - completeOrderSubject = completeOrderSubject.replace("[", "").replace("]", "")
181. Go to My Rewards page
187. VP5: Verify reward detail: lifetime=no change,pending=current pending+reward, redeemable=no change,point value: no change
191. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardPointsDetails
197. VP6: Verify reward history: 1 row with sataut pending,1 row with status processing
201. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardHistory
207. Logout
213. Login As Admin
217. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
223. Go to Woocommerce > Orders > Change order status to Completed
227. beautytap.AdminAction.changeOrderStatus
233. VP7: Verify user recieve notification email with redeemable point
237. beautytap.GeneralAction.verifyEmailExist
241. beautytap.GeneralAction.openEmail
245. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyOrderCompleteEmail
251. Logout
257. Login again
261. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
265. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
271. VP8: Verify notification: You received [#] redeemable points
277. Go to My Rewards page
283. VP9: Verify reward detail: lifetime=lifetime+reward,pending=pending-reward, redeemable=redeemable+reward,point value: associate with reward
287. Statement - newRedeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", redeemable + rewardEarned))
291. Statement - newPointValue = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateLoyaltyPointValue(newRedeemable)
295. beautytap.ShopAction.VerifyRewardPointsDetails
301. VP10: Verify reward history: 1 row with sataut complete
305. beautytap.GeneralAction.logout