1. Statement - username = USER_EMAIL
5. Statement - password = USER_PASSWORD
9. Statement - productName = SIMPLE_PRODUCT
13. Statement - price = SIMPLE_PRODUCT_PRICE
17. Statement - quantity = 3
21. Statement - shippingLabel = FREE_SHIPPING_LABEL
25. Statement - shippingPrice = 0
29. Statement - subtotal = CustomKeywords.beautytap.ShopAction.calculateTotal(quantity, price)
33. Statement - total = subtotal + shippingPrice
37. Statement - products = new org.json.JSONArray((((((([{"productname":" + productName) + ","variation":"","quantity":") + quantity) + ","price":") + price) + "}]))
41. Statement - billingInformation = new org.json.JSONObject((({"firstname":"Test","lastname":"Automation","country":"United States (US)","address":"123 Testing","city":"New York","state":"New York","zip":"90012","email":" + username) + "}))
45. Statement - paymentMethod = "Credit Card Payment"
49. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
53. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
57. beautytap.GeneralAction.login
61. beautytap.GeneralAction.selectProfileMenu
67. Get current multiplier, lifetime, pending, redeemable points, point value
71. Statement - multiplier = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objRewoard.get("multiplier"))
75. Statement - currentlevel = objRewoard.get("currentlevel")
79. Statement - lifetime = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objRewoard.get("lifetime"))
83. Statement - pending = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objRewoard.get("pending"))
87. Statement - redeemable = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objRewoard.get("redeemable"))
91. Statement - pointvalue = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(objRewoard.get("pointvalue"))
95. Statement - rewardEarned = java.lang.Float.parseFloat(java.lang.String.format("%.2f", multiplier * subtotal))
99. Statement - notificationMessage = "You received " + rewardEarned + " redeemable points"
105. Buy a product
109. beautytap.ShopAction.selectProductOnSearchResult
113. beautytap.ShopAction.addProductToCart
117. beautytap.ShopAction.goToCart
123. Process to checkout
127. beautytap.ShopAction.fillCustomerInformation
133. VP1: Verify order details on checkout
139. VP2: Verify reward on checkout page: Rewards earned = (subtotal-discount)*multiplier
143. beautytap.ShopAction.checkoutViaCreditCard
149. VP3: Verify order details on Order Recieved