1. Statement - r_string = new java.lang.Math().random().toString().substring(2, 8)
5. Statement - username = "auto" + r_string
9. Statement - email = username + "@mailinator.com"
13. Statement - password = "123456"
17. Statement - newpassword = "test123"
21. Statement - name = "Auto User " + r_string
25. Statement - birthday = "01/01/1990"
29. Statement - activation_subject = SITE_TITLE + " Activate your account"
33. Statement - resetpass_subject = SITE_TITLE + " Password Reset"
37. beautytap.GeneralAction.openBeautytap
41. beautytap.GeneralAction.clickNavigationMenu
45. beautytap.GeneralAction.signup
51. VP1: Verify message displays: Registration successful. A verification email has been sent to you. Please check your inbox.
55. beautytap.GeneralAction.openMailBox
61. VP2: Verify activation email exist
65. beautytap.GeneralAction.openEmail